[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was declared the International Year of the Potato by the United Nations?", "correct_answer": "2008", "incorrect_answers": ["2004", "2001", "2006"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which countrys territory does the Dead Sea belong?", "correct_answer": "Israel and Jordan share ownership", "incorrect_answers": ["Egypt and Israel share ownership", "Israels territory", "Saudi Arabias territory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the two characters speaking in the audio soundbite from the movie Airplane!.", "correct_answer": "Dr. Rumak and Elaine", "incorrect_answers": ["Randy and Steve McCroskey", "Ted Striker and Randy", "Steve McCroskey and Elaine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Egypt called Kemet, or black land, back in the ancient times?", "correct_answer": "Because of the black soils", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of the coal", "Because of the petrol", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of pure gold, which it maintains without oxidizing in air and water?", "correct_answer": "Bright yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Pale yellow", "Pale orange-yellow", "Ivory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A vampire bat will die if it doesnt find blood for how many nights in a row?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "1", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Clark Kent/Superman in the 1948 Superman movie?", "correct_answer": "Kirk Alyn", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Larsen", "George Reeves", "Christopher Reeves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first people to settle Madagascar came from Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to orbit the Earth?", "correct_answer": "Yuri Gagarin", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgi Dobrovolski", "Neil Armstrong", "Kerim Kerimov"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what U.S. state is the tallest waterfall in the country, Waihilau Falls, located?", "correct_answer": "Hawaii", "incorrect_answers": ["Idaho", "Wyoming", "Iowa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This drama is set in 1952 and is listed as the 4th best sports film of all time by the American Film Institute.", "correct_answer": "Hoosiers", "incorrect_answers": ["Field of Dreams", "Rudy", "Rocky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of flour is used for the preparation of the Thai bread Khanom bueang?", "correct_answer": "Rice flour", "incorrect_answers": ["Potato flour", "Corn flour", "Wheat flour"]}]